hey guys now we're going to add up some
vectors the first one is asking for it
in component form this right here is
component form if three is and four J's
so when adding vectors all you do is
just add the corresponding component so
3 plus 7 is 10 I and negative 4 plus 3
is negative 1 and there's the answer to
a now if we want to show it as a
magnitude in a direction the way that
you find the magnitude is you do the
square root of this squared plus this
squared
and that's the magnitude square root of
101 then to find the direction so you do
tangent inverse of negative 1 over 10
which is equal to negative five point
seven degrees and then it right after
you do this you want to check your
quadrant so 10 i minus J is down here so
negative 5.7 makes sense so then this
would be written as agne tude equals
square root of 101 and the direction is
negative five point seven degrees that's
it hope that helped talk to you later
bye